[Music]
[Applause]
oopsie
looks like my bros got a serious case of
the stinky and smelly shits
i better roll down the window and get
some fresh air running throughout the
car
[Laughter]
oh come on don't be like that lil bro
it's really smelly back here because of
you
oh gee don't be such a whiner bro it's
not that bad you've been through worse
bro did you [ __ ] [ __ ] yourself
mama why are you wearing your crown
today
it makes me feel like I'm not worthless
don't look at it
okay
bro stop mom make him stop rolling the
window back up it's stinky back here
Manic stop picking on your brother i
swear to God
if you left another poopy stain in my
family van we are not
stopping by the arcade after I pick you
up from Uncle Chuck's
bro what are you just sitting around for
we need to clean this up with what we
are Hedgehogs we have hands
quick shove it into the butt crack of
the seats
it's not working stop what you're doing
and act
like it's not even there if we're lucky
maybe she won't even notice it's there
[Music]
okay we'll hear it Uncle Chuck's place
everyone got what they need
um mom are you sure this is the right
neighborhood this isn't how Uncle Chuck
described it
of course I am do you really think i
would get the address wrong for my own
brother's house
but where's the swimming pool and the
big garden he said he had in his front
yard
swimming pool oh you must mean that
public fuel across the street
he likes to tell people he has one
because he thinks it helps him pick up
[ __ ]
hey look there's Uncle Chuck right now
maybe he can explain what's going on
hi Uncle Chuck happy 4th of July
how have you been
ready
you got it this is gonna be fun
alrighty kids I'm leaving now have fun
with Uncle Chuck
don't hesitate to call if you need
anything
Uncle Chuck happy 4th of July we're here
for the BBQ
spent
hey what's the meaning of this uncle you
said you live in a huge three-story
house
yeah what's up with that hunk domingo
man
the steps three
whoa look at that what's going on next
door
check out that awesome BBQ and do you
see that slip and slide in the front
lawn
that's our Uncle Chuck does that mean
you got the premium hot dogs for this
occasion
we can't let them outshine us after all
oh
yeah the premium
you think you want us to look for it
alone this is your house
there is nothing wrong with that history
oh crap uncle when you put it that way i
guess we don't got a choice then
you don't recall no butterfield
okay Josh Uncle Chuck just went outside
you remember the plan don't you uncle
Chuck wanted us to jump out
and surprise his niece and nephews with
a surprise concert for the 4th of July
what song are you going to sing what do
you expect [ __ ]
the same one I always do the Drake and
Josh theme song
nobody cares about any of my other music
now let's hurry and go out there before
they leave their uncle said
he'll pay us 16
i can't find any gasoline anywhere any
luck on your end pro
as if all of these bottles are empty I'm
beginning to think Uncle Chuck pranked
us
what's he plotting he he hey you know
what would be so [ __ ] funny
what you remember when Uncle Chuck hired
Drake Bell for Mindy sweet 16th birthday
party
oh my God don't even remind me that was
so [ __ ] sad
like imagine if Uncle Chuck did that
again today but like
for the 4th of July okay now you're just
being [ __ ] Drake Bell isn't even a
good singer
i know that because I'm the leader of
the Sonic Underground band
Drake is is everything okay
the only reason Mindy listens to Drake
Bella is because her taste in music is
stinky crap
haha can't argue with that one but you
know what would be cool
the Jonas brothers now you're talking
says
there's like three brothers so by
default they're at least three times
better than Drake Bell
God I [ __ ] hate Drake Bell what the
[ __ ] wannabe poser
he's not even a real rock star what kind
of name is Drake Bell anyway
it sounds like Drake balls which is
fitting because his music sucks big fat
juicy balls
come on Drake let's go out there and
surprise them
[Music]
i I think it's better if you go out by
yourself i'll just
i'll just sneak out around back when you
get their attention
what but we're Drake and Josh we're a
duo they won't be happy with just me
you have to be there to sing the hit
Drake and Josh song I found a way and
for what
Josh so they can laugh at me that's not
how this is going down
i am not leaving this closet
uh
Uncle Chuck when are you going to make
the hot dogs the people across the
street have those really good ones with
cheese in the middle
my bro is right Uncle Chuck and where
are the hamburgers
what's the point of grilling out if you
are not even going to make hamburgers
you can't afford that [ __ ] okay as you
can afford the bucket belts
lie off me
well then I guess it's a good thing my
bro always carries around a nice big
pack of winners
isn't that right my bro
haha come on Sonic let it go
you're going to have to pull harder than
that bro
yo bro how's the hot dog [ __ ] this food
bus in bro
what the [ __ ] did y'all host say about
me cooking boy
let go of me old man I was just saying
your food was busan
no cap yo kids and your disrespectful
mother and I straight up the only couple
here let go of my bro you crazy [ __ ] we
were just doing a cool tick-tock trend
let go of him I said let go of my green
bro
finniten if this is all your kids are
going to act
you wish you would never come to visit
since your world retirement
you really mean it Uncle Chuck can we
really go play next door
only if you're feeling with breaking
your own cletus power holder
i wanna jump on the bouncy castle
[Music]
Uncle Chuck is everything okay why are
you crying
dracula it's nothing
it just have a lot of memories get back
into closet
[Music]
[Applause]
ted
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
is when striping sees
Sonic Manic look over there fireworks
Uncle Chuck are you seeing this oh
that's right
Uncle Chuck went back inside I sure wish
Uncle Chuck could watch the fireworks
with
us he always does love fireworks and 4th
of July is his favorite holiday
after all
[Music]
yes what is it [ __ ] I'm in the middle
of something important so make it as
quick as
i destroy your fat ass with my massive
[ __ ] balls
yes I will be quick Bartleby I I'm just
sad
and I need somebody to talk to right now
well we can't have that knock and we
because when my cute little [ __ ] is sad
then so am i
i agree with Nick Jonas this one tastes
like somebody took a massive [ __ ]
poopy in it
i don't like that um Bartleby what are
you doing
I'm taste testing expensive cottage
cheese at a cottage cheese factory
it is going to be the most expensive
cottage cheese in the world
when it goes on sale only rich people
like me and Nick Jonas can buy it
whoa how much is it going to cost don't
worry about it
you couldn't afford it anyway now tell
me why you're sad [ __ ]
well me and my sibs came over to my
Uncle Chuck's house to celebrate 4th of
July
yes I know of the poor man's holiday
that is 4th of July
we thought it would be really fun but
turns out all Uncle Chuck had planned
was to grill out beans
i ended up getting in a fight with him
and now he won't come out of the house
Bartleby tell me was was I in the wrong
but I mean it's 4th of July he should
have thrown a better party
right the old man didn't even buy
fireworks or have anything fun planned
Bartleby if it's all right can I speak
to your boyfriend for just a second
no Sonic the Hedgehog how you doing
well Nick Jonas it's really you what you
want
listen Sonic I want to tell you
something from one badass
and sexy musician to another your uncle
Chuck invited you over to his house for
a reason
it's cause he loves you he wants to
spend 4th of July with you
even though he doesn't have enough money
for fireworks or food
that should count for something right
not every uncle would do that
thank you Nick Jonas thank you I have to
go now
i need to hurry and apologize to my
Uncle Chuck
though and can you tell Bartleby I love
him
it looks like everything is going to be
okay Bartleby your boyfriend really is a
good boy
oh and by the way Sonic wanted me to
tell you that he wants you to [ __ ] him
really hard when you get home
and that he also wants you to record the
whole thing and send me a copy
uh-huh Nick Jonas super vert my [ __ ]
didn't say that
i heard the whole thing haha well you
can't blame a guy for trying
[Music]
well we did but to tell you the truth we
feel really awful for what we put you
through
yet we know how much you like 4th of
July and we kind of ruined your special
day
that's alright you live in arsenal
semi-friends they are blown up in order
to protect this country that yoshita
yoga
but what made you change
because we realized it's not about the
things you want it's about the things
that you do have
and to cherish them holds them dear
because those things are what matter
most of all in the world
you see there will always be things you
want but you don't have to throw your
family away to get them
especially if that family is the coolest
uncle ever
time for what Uncle Chuck did you buy
premium hamburger patties
even better sony you told
nothing special planet for quadrotic of
politician
that called the forte from tetr festio
regia sometime I never come on
boys
oh um look at that it's it's certainly
Drake Bell
are the Jonas brothers behind him Drake
Bell move over a bit
no it's just him oh
well go on play your song or whatever
you are going to do so we can get this
over with
wait you're not disappointed I mean
yeah we are but you're already here so
there's nothing we can do about it now
is there
okay good enough for me
[Music]
it's gonna take some time to realize
[Applause]
you know you gotta live how you wanna
live
when it's time to be free
to know you gotta be what you wanna be
you